Preliminary Guide to the History of Political Economy Records, 1967-2011 RL.00551
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
History of Political Economy records
1967-2011
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
History of political economy
RL.00551
128.9 Linear Feet
16,000 Items
Access Restrictions
RESTRICTED: Items are restricted except by written permission for 25 years from the date of creation.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The History of Political Economy Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a transfer and gift in 1998-2011.
Biographical Note
Scholarly journal on the history of economic thought. Founded in 1967 and published by Duke University Press.
Collection Overview
Collection (1998-0229, 1998-0450, 1998-0455, 1999-0318, 1999-0365, 2000-0152, 2000-0184) (11950 items, 109.6 lin. ft.; dated 1967-1999) contains the files of published and unpublished manuscripts on the history of economics, arranged for the most part in chronological groupings and then alphabetically by author, along with referees' comments and editors' correspondence.
The addition (2001-0018) (100 items, 0.3 lin. ft.; dated 1995-1998) contains 23 manuscripts accepted for publication and their associated correspondence.
The addition (2001-119) (450 items, 0.6 lin. ft.; dated 1995-2000) comprises files of published and rejected manuscripts. There is also information pertaining to the founding of the journal.
The addition (2001-0180) (200 items, 1.5 lin. ft.; dated 1998-2001) contains rejected manuscripts.
The addition (2001-0194) (150 items, 1.0 lin. ft.; dated 1995-2001) contains 40 manuscripts accepted for publication and their associated correspondence. Five manuscripts included machine-readable records.
The addition (2001-0261) (525 items, 0.8 lin. ft.; dated 1994-1999) contains correspondence related to published and unpublished articles, primarily for volume 32. Includes 1 electronic document received on one floppy disk.
The addition (2002-0172) (1500 items, 3.0 lin. ft.; dated 1997-2002) comprises correspondence related to articles published in volumes 31.4, 33.2, and 34.2 as well as rejected articles. There are also folders related to HOPE conferences (1997-1999).
The addition (2003-0140) (130 items, 0.6 lin. ft.; dated 2000-2003) includes published manuscripts for the Spring and Fall 2003 issues, as well as rejected manuscripts.
The addition (2003-0186) (375 items; 0.6 lin. ft.; dated 1997-2003) consists of records for issues 32.1, 32.2, 34.1, 34.3, 34.4, and 35.1, including published and rejected manuscripts, and correspondence.
The addition (2004-0100) (250 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 2000-2004) consists of files containing rejected manuscripts, primarily from 2002-2003, along with related correspondence and readers' reports.
The addition (2006-0059) (1875 items; 3.0 lin. ft.; dated 2004-2005) contains files of unpublished and rejected manuscripts with related correspondence and peer reviews; and files of accepted manuscripts for issues 36.2, 36.3, 36.4, 37.2, and 37.4.
The addition (2007-0163) (950 items; 1.4 lin. ft.; dated 2003-2006) contains files of articles submitted for publication and correspondence, peer reviews, and revisions related to these articles. Also included are submissions that were rejected from publication.
The addition (2007-0164) (450 items; 0.8 lin. ft.; dated 2005-2006) includes manuscripts, revisions, and correspondence for articles published in issues 39.4 and 40.1; and rejected manuscripts.
The addition (2008-0265) (750 items; 1 lin. ft.; dated 2008) includes correspondence, manuscripts, and revisions for articles published in issues 40.1 and 40.2; also rejected manuscripts.
The addition (2008-0315) (900 items; 1.5 lin. ft.; dated 2006-2008) includes rejected manuscripts and accepted articles for issues 41.1 and 41.2.
The addition (2009-0167) (800 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 2008-2009) includes rejected manuscripts and accepted articles for issues 41.3 and 41.4.
The addition (2010-0085) (900 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 2008-2010) includes accepted and rejected manuscripts from issues 42.3.
The addition (2010-0124) (100 items; 0.2 lin. ft.; dated 2006-2010) includes correspondence between HOPE editors and authors regarding accepted articles for issue 42.4
The addition (2011-1007) (200 items; 0.5 lin. ft.; dated 2011-2012) includes accepted articles and papers for issues 43.3, 43.4, and 44.1.
Machine-readable records; Economics -- Philosophy; Economics -- History; Periodical editors -- United States -- Correspondence; Editors -- United States -- Correspondence; Economics -- History -- Periodicals; Economics
- Accession (1998-0229)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  RESTRICTED: Written permission is required for use of materials 25 years from their date of creation. Patrons must also sign a statement about release of information regardless of date of records.
  - Contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    [Duke University Archives Accession #78-112]
    - 1969-1974, Accepted Manuscripts, A-G (Box 1)
  - Contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    - 1969-1974, Accepted Manuscripts, H-Mon (Box 2)
  - Contents of Box 3: (Box 3)
    - 1969-1974, Accepted Manuscripts, Mos-Z (Box 3)
  - Contents of Box 4: (Box 4)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #80-208]
    - 1975-1978, Accepted Manuscripts, A-J (Box 4)
  - Contents of Box 5: (Box 5)
    - 1975-1978, Accepted Manuscripts, K-Tho (Box 5)
  - Contents of Box 6: (Box 6)
    - 1975-1978, Accepted Manuscripts, Thw-Z (Box 6)
  - Contents of Box 7: (Box 7)
    - 1968-1977, Rejected Manuscripts, A-C (Box 7)
  - Contents of Box 8: (Box 8)
    - 1968-1977, Rejected Manuscripts, D-Hi (Box 8)
  - Contents of Box 9: (Box 9)
    - 1968-1977, Rejected Manuscripts, Hj-Mh (Box 9)
  - Contents of Box 10: (Box 10)
    - 1968-1977, Rejected Manuscripts, Mi-Sa (Box 10)
  - Contents of Box 11: (Box 11)
    - 1968-1977, Rejected Manuscripts, Sc-Z (Box 11)
  - Contents of Box 12: (Box 12)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #82-129]
    - 1979-1980, Accepted Manuscripts, A-G (Box 12)
  - Contents of Box 13: (Box 13)
    - 1979-1980, Accepted Manuscripts, H-O (Box 13)
  - Contents of Box 14: (Box 14)
    - 1979-1980, Accepted Manuscripts, P-Z (Box 14)
  - Contents of Box 15: (Box 15)
    - 1978-1980, Rejected Manuscripts, A-H (Box 15)
  - Contents of Box 16: (Box 16)
    - 1978-1980, Rejected Manuscripts, I-P (Box 16)
  - Contents of Box 17: (Box 17)
    - 1978-1980, Rejected Manuscripts, R-Z (Box 17)
  - Contents of Box 18: (Box 18)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #84-36]
    - 1981-1982, Accepted Manuscripts, A-Mic (Box 18)
  - Contents of Box 19: (Box 19)
    - 1981-1982, Accepted Manuscripts, Mir-Y (Box 19)
  - Contents of Box 20: (Box 20)
    - 1981, Rejected Manuscripts, A-T (Box 20)
  - Contents of Box 21: (Box 21)
    - 1981, Rejected Manuscripts, U-Z (Box 21)
    - 1982, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Z (Box 21)
  - Contents of Box 22: (Box 22)
    - 1983-1984, Accepted Manuscripts, A-Har (Box 22)
  - Contents of Box 23: (Box 23)
    - 1983-1984, Accepted Manuscripts, Hen-R (Box 23)
  - Contents of Box 24: (Box 24)
    - 1983 Rejected Manuscripts, A-R (Box 24)
  - Contents of Box 25: (Box 25)
    - 1983 Rejected Manuscripts, S-Y (Box 25)
    - 1984 Rejected Manuscripts, A-M (Box 25)
  - Contents of Box 26: (Box 26)
    - 1984 Rejected Manuscripts, P-W (Box 26)
  - Contents of Box 27: (Box 27)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #85-39]
    - Foul, manuscripts, Vols. 15.2-16.3, 83:4, and 84:2 (Box 27)
  - Contents of Box 28: (Box 28)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #88-0023]
    - 1982-1985, Accepted Manuscripts, A-K (Box 28)
  - Contents of Box 29: (Box 29)
    - 1982-1985, Accepted Manuscripts, K-V (Box 29)
  - Contents of Box 30: (Box 30)
    - 1982-1985, Accepted Manuscripts, W-Z (Box 30)
    - 1985, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Z (Box 30)
  - Contents of Box 31: (Box 31)
    - 1986, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Z (Box 31)
  - Contents of Box 32: (Box 32)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #90-52]
    - 1987, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Z (Box 32)
  - Contents of Box 33: (Box 33)
    - 1988, Rejected Manuscripts, A-R (Box 33)
  - Contents of Box 34: (Box 34)
    - 1988, Rejected Manuscripts, S-Z (Box 34)
    - 1987-1988, Accepted Manuscripts, A-D (Box 34)
  - Contents of Box 35: (Box 35)
    - 1987-1988, Accepted Manuscripts, E-Sa (Box 35)
  - Contents of Box 36: (Box 36)
    - 1987-1988, Accepted Manuscripts, Sc-Z (Box 36)
  - Contents of Box 37**: (Box 37)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #90-97]
    - Article Folders, Volume 21, A-P (Box 37)
  - Contents of Box 38: (Box 38)
    - Article Folders, Volume 21, P-Z (Box 38)
    - Correspondence
      - Duke Press ( 1969-1983) (Box 38)
      - Reviews ( 1972-1978) (Box 38)
      - Founding of HOPE ( 1968-1973) (Box 38)
    - Books submitted for review 1975-1985 (Box 38)
    - Current Contents (Box 38)
    - Manuscript Log, 1977-1978 (Box 38)
    - Book Review Log, 1975-1982 (Box 38)
    - NSF Symposium Finance (Founding of HOPE) (Box 38)
    - Symposium on the History of Economic Thought (Box 38)
    - NSF Symposium material (Box 38)
    - Symposium Program (Box 38)
    - Invitations to Symposium (Box 38)
    - Progress Report HOPE, 1971 (Box 38)
    - Copenhagen Conference Papers, 1974 (Box 38)
  - Contents of Box 39: (Box 39)
    - Advisory Board Correspondence, 1967-1986** (Box 39)
  - Contents of Box 40: (Box 40)
    - Table of Contents and Abstracts for Volumes 6.1-14.4 (Box 40)
    - Table of Contents and Abstracts for Fall 1970-1975 (Box 40)
  - Contents of Box 41: (Box 41)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #91-98]
    - 1988-1990, Rejected Manuscripts, A-K (Box 41)
  - Contents of Box 42: (Box 42)
    - 1988-1990, Rejected Manuscripts, Kl-Z (Box 42)
  - Contents of Box 43: (Box 43)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #92-100]
    - Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 43)
    - Volumes 22.1-22.2, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 43)
  - Contents of Box 44: (Box 44)
    - Volumes 22.3-22.4, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 44)
  - Contents of Box 45: (Box 45)
    - Volumes 23.1-23.3, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 45)
  - Contents of Box 46: (Box 46)
    - Volumes 23.4 and 23 Special Issue, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 46)
  - Contents of Box 47: (Box 47)
    - 1990-1991, Rejected Manuscripts (Box 47)
  - Contents of Box 48: (Box 48)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #93-91]
    - 1990-1991, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Mes (Box 48)
  - Contents of Box 49: (Box 49)
    - 1990-1991, Rejected Manuscripts, Mes-Y (Box 49)
    - General Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 49)
  - Contents of Box 50: (Box 50)
    - 1992, Vol. 24.1-24.2 and 23 Special Issue, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 50)
  - Contents of Box 51: (Box 51)
    - Volumes 24.2-24.4, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 51)
  - Contents of Box 52: (Box 52)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #94-201]
    - 1992-1993, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Ki (Box 52)
  - Contents of Box 53: (Box 53)
    - 1992-1993, Rejected Manuscripts, Kl-W (Box 53)
  - Contents of Box 54: (Box 54)
    - Volumes 24.4-25.2, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 54)
  - Contents of Box 55: (Box 55)
    - Volumes 25.3-25.SI, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 55)
  - Contents of Box 56: (Box 56)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #95-103]
    - 1994, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Z (Box 56)
  - Contents of Box 57: (Box 57)
    - Volumes 26.1-26.4, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 57)
  - Contents of Box 58: (Box 58)
    [Duke University Archives Accession #96-109]
    - 1994-1995, Rejected Manuscripts, A-Ke (Box 58)
  - Contents of Box 59: (Box 59)
    - 1994-1995, Rejected Manuscripts, Kh-Z (Box 59)
  - Contents of Box 60: (Box 60)
    - Volumes 26.SI-27.2, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 60)
  - Contents of Box 61: (Box 61)
    - Volumes 27.3-27.SI, Accepted Manuscripts (Box 61)
    - General Correspondence 1991-1993 (Box 61)
  - Contents of Box 62: (Box 62)
    [Rubenstein Library, Duke University Accession #1998-0229]
    - Table of Contents and Abstracts, 15.1-24.4 (Box 62)
  - Contents of Box 63: (Box 63)
    - Volumes 28.1-28.3, Accepted Articles (Box 63)
  - Contents of Box 64: (Box 64)
    - Volumes 28.4 and 28.SI, Accepted Articles (Box 64)
  - Contents of Box 65: (Box 65)
    - 1995-1996, Rejected Articles, A-Z (Box 65)
- Accession (1998-0450)
  - Rejected Manuscripts, A-L, 1995 Aug.-1997 Aug. (Box 1)
  - Rejected Manuscripts, M-Z, 1995 Aug.-1997 Aug. (Box 2)
  - Published Articles (Box 3)
    - HOPE 29.1 (Box 3)
    - HOPE 29.2 (Box 3)
    - HOPE 29.3 (Box 3)
    - HOPE 29.4 (Box 3)
    - HOPE 29 Special Issue (Box 3)
    - HOPE 30.1 (Box 4)
    - HOPE 30.2 (Box 4)
    - HOPE 30 Special Issue (Box 4)
  - Table of Contents and Abstracts
    - HOPE 30 Special Issue (Box 4)
    - HOPE 30.2 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 30.1 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 29 Special Issue (Box 5)
    - HOPE 29.4 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 29.3 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 29.2 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 29.1 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 28 Special Issue (Box 5)
    - HOPE 28.4 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 28.3 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 28.2 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 28.1 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 27 Special Issue (Box 5)
    - HOPE 27.4 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 27.3 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 27.2 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 27.1 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 26 Special Issue (Box 5)
    - HOPE 26.4 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 26.3 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 26.2 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 26.1 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 25 Special Issue (Box 5)
    - HOPE 25.4 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 25.3 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 25.2 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 25.1 (Box 5)
    - HOPE 24 Special Issue (Box 5)
- Accession (2001-0018)
  RESTRICTED: Written permission is required for 25 years from the date of the creation of records. Signed statement about release of information is required regardless of the date of the record.
  - box 1 (Box 1)
    - 31.1
      - Samuels, Warren (Box 1)
      - Brewer, Anthony (Box 1)
      - Darity, William Jr. (Box 1)
      - Louca, Francisco (Box 1)
      - Klein, Judy L. (Box 1)
      - Samuels, Warren J. (Box 1)
      - Larson, Bruce (Box 1)
      - Arnon, Arie (Box 1)
      - Moore, Gregory (Box 1)
      - Emmett, Ross (Box 1)
      - Fontaine, Philippe (Box 1)
    - 30.3
      - Witztum, Amos (Box 1)
      - Whatmore, Richard (Box 1)
      - Syll, Lars Palsson (Box 1)
      - Maneschi, Andrea (Box 1)
      - Nightingale, John (Box 1)
      - Kurer, Oskar (Box 1)
      - Horwitz, Steven (Box 1)
      - Horwitz, Steven (Box 1)
    - 30.4
      - Aslanbeigui, Nihad and Steven Madema (Box 1)
      - Caldwell, Bruce (Box 1)
      - Hosseini, Hamid (Box 1)
      - Persky, Joseph (Box 1)
      - Waterman, A.M.C. (Box 1)
- Accession (2001-0261)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Electronic records in this series have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact Research Services before coming to use these records.
  - Frey, Donald, 1999; 2 Megabytes; 1 disk image derived from 3.5" floppy disk; approximately 2 megabytes.
    Scope and Contents
    Includes an article, 'The Puritan Roots of Daniel Raymond's Economics'.
- Accession (2002-0172)
  - Rejected manuscripts, A-F, 1999-2002 (Box 1)
  - Rejected manuscripts, G-M, 1998-2001 (Box 2)
  - Rejected manuscripts, N-S, 1999-2002 (Box 3)
  - Rejected manuscripts, T-Y, 1999-2002 (Box 4)
  - Articles for 33.2 (summer 2001) (Box 4)
  - HOPE conferences, 1997-1998 (Box 4)
  - HOPE conferences, 1998-1999 (Box 5)
  - Articles for 31.4 (Box 5)
  - Articles for 34.2 (Box 5)
- Accession (2003-0140)
  - Accepted and rejected manuscripts, 2003 (Box 1)
- Accession (2003-0186)
  - Issues 32.1, 32.2, 34.1, 34.3, 34.4, and 35.1 (Box 1)
- Accession (2004-0100)
  - Rejected manuscripts, 2002-2003 (Box 1-2)
- Accession (2006-0059)
  - Accepted and rejected manuscripts (Box 1-5)
- Accessions (2007-0163) and (2007-0164)
  - Submissions, correspondence, revisions (Box 1)
  - Rejected submissions and correspondence (Box 2)
  - Rejected submissions and correspondence (Box 3)
  - Submissions, correspondence, revisions for articles published in issues 39.4 and 40.1 (Box 4)
  - Rejected submissions and correspondence (Box 5)
- Accession (2008-0265)
  - Manuscripts for issues 40.1 and 40.2, and rejected submissions (Box 1)
- Accession (2008-0315)
  - Rejected manuscripts (Box 1)
  - Accepted manuscripts, issues 41.1-41.2 (Spring-Summer, 2009) (Box 1)
- Accession (2009-0167), 2 boxes
  Addition (2009-0167) (800 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 2008-2009) includes rejected manuscripts and accepted articles, filed under last name, for issues 41.3 and 41.4.
  - Rejected manuscripts (Box 1)
  - Rejected manuscripts (Box 2)
  - Accepted manuscripts, issues 41.3-41.4 (Fall-Winter, 2009) (Box 2)
- Accession (2009-0230), 1 box
  Addition (2009-230) (900 items; 1.5 lin. ft.; dated 2008-2009) includes rejected manuscripts, filed by last name.
  - Rejected manuscripts, 2008-2009 (Box 1)
- Accession (2009-0254), 1 box
  Addition (2009-0254) (500 items; 0.6 lin. ft.; dated 2007-2009) includes accepted manuscripts for issues 40.4 and 42.2.
  - Accepted manuscripts, 40.4 (Box 1)
  - Accepted manuscripts, 42.2 (Box 1)
- Accession (2010-085), 2 boxes
  Addition (2010-0085) (900 items; 1.2 lin. ft.; dated 2008-2010) includes accepted and rejected manuscripts from issues 42.3.
  - Rejected manuscripts, 42.3 (Box 1)
  - Rejected manuscripts, 42.3 (Box 2)
  - Accepted manuscripts, 42.3 (Box 2)
- Accession (2010-0124), 1 box
  The addition (2010-0124) (100 items; 0.2 lin. ft.; dated 2006-2009) includes correspondence between HOPE editors and authors regarding accepted articles for issue 42.4
  - Dixon, William, and Wilson, David (Box 1)
  - Ambrosi, G.M. (Box 1)
  - Bliss, Christopher (Box 1)
  - Camic, Charles (Box 1)
  - Van Horn, Robert (Box 1)
  - Silvermintz, Daniel (Box 1)
  - Forget, Evelyn (Box 1)
- Accession (2011-1007), 1 box
  The addition (2011-1007) (200 items; 0.5 lin. ft.; dated 2011-2012) includes correspondence between editors and authors of accepted articles and papers for issues 43.3, 43.4, and 44.1.
  - Issue 43.3 (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Ferreira, d'Aspremont and Gerard-Varet (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Aslanbeigri and Oahes (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Platon, Mercea (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Leonard, Tim (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Kurz and Salvadori (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Garegnani, P. (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
  - Issue 43.4 (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Singleton, John (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Heukelon, Floris (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Meoqui (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Repapis, Constantinos (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Rangil, Teresa T. (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
  - Issue 44.1 (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Weintraub, E. Roy (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Fleury, Jean-Baptiste (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Numa (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Ekeland and Hebat (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Ormazabal, Kepa (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
    - Lenfant (Box 1, Acc. 11/1007)
- Accession (2012-0066) and (2012-0182), 1 box
  Accepted papers and correspondence for Summer, Fall, and Winter 2012 issues.
  - Issue 44.2 (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Littlechild, Stephen (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Trescott, Kathleen (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Rubin, Goulven (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Fontaine, Philippe (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Boianovsky, Mauro (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
  - Issue 44.3 (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Duppe, Till (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Ekelunel and Hebert (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Kapuria-Foreman/McCann (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Berry, Christopher (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Skaggs, Neil (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
  - Issue 44.4 (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Le Maux, Laurent (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Cardoso and Cunha (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)
    - Meacci, Ferdinando (Box 1, Acc. 12/066)